{
    "subject": "resource/Valeriy_Khoroshkovskyi",
    "predicate": "ontology/office",
    "object": "First Vice Prime Minister of Ukraine",
    "human_readable": "Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi holds the office of First Vice Prime Minister of Ukraine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9031981229782104,
            "question": "What position does Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi hold in Ukraine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8415529131889343,
            "question": "Is Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi involved in Ukrainian politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8284145593643188,
            "question": "Who is Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6736910343170166,
            "question": "Which country's government is Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6382657289505005,
            "question": "What challenges might a First Vice Prime Minister face in Ukraine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6197013854980469,
            "question": "How has Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi's role impacted Ukrainian policy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5591904520988464,
            "question": "Who is the Prime Minister of Ukraine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4270016551017761,
            "question": "What are the responsibilities of a First Vice Prime Minister?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26463228464126587,
            "question": "What is the name of Ukraine's current government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1306106448173523,
            "question": "What are some key issues facing Ukraine today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi holds the office of First Vice Prime Minister of Ukraine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1130_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ukraine's current government?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1130_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the responsibilities of a First Vice Prime Minister?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1130_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the Prime Minister of Ukraine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1130_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1130_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple. The context information mentions that President Yanukovych appointed Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi as First Vice Prime Minister of Ukraine, and subsequent texts confirm this appointment, mentioning his responsibilities and activities in this role."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Valeriy Khoroshkovskyi served as the First Vice Prime Minister of Ukraine. Specifically, multiple documents confirm his appointment to this position on February 22, 2012."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}